We'll have to swap out 10,000 square
meters of ground surface unit.
One Week Later
Fourteen commercial buildings were
partially or completely destroyed.
Damage to six other sectors as well.
The underground lifelines
were affected as well,
but they will be repaired soon.
We were lucky the enemy
landed in a commercial area.
Not many people were out since
it was a weekday afternoon,
which kept casualties to a minimum.
Kizuna!
Kizuna-kun!
I'm back, everyone.
Are your injuries all right now?
Yeah.
I can't stay in bed any longer.
She was far stronger than Aldea,
the one you fought in Guam.
Grabel
I want to wait for further analysis about the
Magitech armor and combat capabilities...
...of the woman from the other dimension
who attacked Ataraxia, Grabel.
What's most important now...
...is that the enemy's target
was Zeros, as well as Aine.
Why would they be after Zeros and Aine?
Aine, do you know?
No.
I'd like to know myself.
Aine...
To take back Japan, we need to close
the Tokyo and Okinawa entrances.
We've headed north from Guam,
and we are presently
500km southeast of Okinawa.
We'll start by sealing the Okinawa entrance.
But Grabel is there.
We'll have to defeat her
if we want to take back Japan.
She's strong.
We'll need a new Hybrid to defeat her:
the Connective Hybrid.
Connective Hybrid?
A Connective Hybrid is when
Eros and two other units
engage in a simultaneous Hybrid Heart.
Wow!
In other words...
The energy created is overwhelming.
It allows for a more powerful
offensive energy charge than
the normal Heart Hybrid.
That sounds fun!
It's the same as a Climax Hybrid.
You'll be able to acquire
a more powerful Immoral Weapon
via the Connective Hybrid.
We'll have to go that hard?
What in the world are you
trying to make us do?
Doing it with another girl...
That's so lewd! I just can't!
The Heart Hybrid and Climax Hybrid
unite two hearts and bodies
to share both love and pleasure.
But if you want to power up,
a new form of stimulation
and a greater feeling of depravity
would prove more effective.
The Connective Hybrid makes
both of them possible.
Th-That's so indecent! It's immoral!
That's not all.
The Connective Hybrid uses a
new kind of emotional energy...
...that the previous ones haven't.
The double love Kizuna
feels for both of them,
and the friendship and
trust between the girls.
The result of these emotions
and their combination,
which is impossible with a Heart Hybrid,
allows for greater power
than you would attain alone.
Then I suggest Yurishia and Scarlet.
Episode 8
Connective Hybrid
If only I were stronger...
Scarlet, I'm sorry to
call you out of the blue,
but can you come with me for a while?
We have a new training facility that
will help you power up in a flash.
Power up in a flash?
How is this a training facility
that lets you power up?!
Mobile
Hybrid Special
Bath Mk. 2
Mobile Hybrid Special Bath Mk. 2
And you didn't say anything
about Yurishia being here!
If you're going to power up, it's better
to do so both at once, right?
I-Is this what a H-Heart Hybrid is like?
If this is enough make you embarrassed,
you're still a kid.
I'm so happy I get to
take a bath with Kizuna.
But, Yurishia,
it's kind of bad if you get that close to me.
Get off each other, you two!
You okay, Scarlet?
Y-Yurishia?
I want to hear the sound
of Kizuna's heart beat, too.
S-So soft...
Your back's pretty sensitive, isn't it?
It's ticklish, but it kinda feels good...
Kizuna!
I don't think I can do this!
I'm also kind of...
No, I can't!
No!
What is this?
Something's happening inside me...
It's so gentle and warm.
Okay, we're going to the next stage.
My whole body feels warm...
Take yours off, too, Scarlet.
K-Kizuna, you, too.
O-Okay...
What's wrong?
Do you want to play with them?
I-I just l-lost my balance...
Oh my.
You always used to follow me around
and call me Yurishia-senpai, right?
I figured that's what you used to be like.
Wh-What is this?
I asked Shikina-san to get me
old footage of you two.
Why did you do that?
Oh, Kizuna...
That's when I started fighting
together with Yurishia.
We trained together.
We laughed together.
We cried together.
Yurishia-senpai...
You weren't the kind of person who'd do that.
You wouldn't betray us.
You wouldn't use us as pawns.
So why?
Yurishia.
You actually didn't know the Dragorie
was going to appear, did you?
Answer me, Yurishia.
The enemy had attacked an urban area.
There was a risk that Scarlet's missiles
could miss and hit the town and the people.
If civilians died because of that,
I didn't think she'd ever recover.
So...
I lied to get her and the others away.
You lied?
I hear there's an enemy attack
from a new Entrance!
I'll stay here to fight the enemy.
So you...
Okay!
I'll head there now!
I didn't know the enemy was
really going to appear.
But it's a fact that in the end
I took all the credit for myself.
It's still true that I used you
to become a super ace.
That's right.
She hadn't been attacked
by the Dragorie even once.
She was hurt because she'd been
fighting other enemies on her own.
And she came for us anyway!
Now let's attack Kizuna together.
Okay, Kizuna.
Grab both of us tight!
Okay!
Does that feel good?
Yeah...
Of course it does.
Kizuna, don't forget about me, either.
I need to make them feel good, too.
W-Wow!
No... No more!
Okay!
The Connective Hybrid's almost complete!
Kizuna, I feel weird!
I don't know what's going on!
There's an ache inside my body...
I want to feel you closer to me...
Which will you choose?
We recommend both.
What do I pick? Yurishia? Scarlet?
Don't panic. Think calmly.
This is a Connective Hybrid.
You can't just choose one!
What is this?
I'm filled with power...
This is a Climax Hybrid.
No, a Connective Hybrid, isn't it?
Looks like it worked, Kizuna.
Yeah.
Today, we'll split into two teams
for the operation.
We'll attack Grabel and seal the Entrance
at the same time.
Roger!
Let's go! Eros!
Kuros!
Ares!
H-Hey, Yurishia...
What?
If you really want,
I can let you be leader of the Masters.
Nuh-uh.
You're the leader of the Masters,
aren't you, Scarlet?
And, right now,
I'm Yurishia Farandole of Amaterasu.
We're ready to go whenever.
No, this time they'll come to us.
They'll come. I know it.
They're here?
I've been waiting!
I'll take good care of you.
You're Grabel, right?
I want to ask you something.
Ask me what?
Why are you trying to take me with you?
Silver hair, red eyes.
And the Zeros you wield.
You're—
Aine, are you okay?
Let us handle those two!
We'll pay them back for last time!
You defend the Entrance sealing system!
There are too many of them
for Kizuna and the others.
Fine!
I won't let you go.
Scarlet!
Roger!
Shoot!
So many!
My, not bad!
Now, Yurishia! Go ahead!
Leave it to me.
Cross Head.
That's...
...Yurishia's...
...Immoral Weapon!
Aldea!
Drive!
You did it! You did it, Yurishia!
I'm not the type who likes to keep losing.
You're so amazing, Yurishia!
No...
She survived that?
I will bring my full powers
to bear against you.
This is my real weapon, the Sword Gatling.
Kizuna!
Are you two okay?
You're the man from before?
Why are you trying to take Aine with you?
I see no reason to answer that.
Kuros Mode!
Come, Grabel!
Very well!
What I need is enough firepower
to defeat her weapon.
A gun,
a rifle,
a cannon,
a machine gun,
a rail gun,
a particle gun,
the Differential Flame...
I want them!
Wh-What?
Is he carrying an entire
military force on his back?
Go, Sword Gatling!
I'm coming, too!
Kuros's light...
So I can't overwhelm him with this?
That's not good enough!
More!
I need more!
I need more firepower...
Like Scarlet's...
Hybrid Mode!
Ares's missiles...
How could I... lose...?
Kizuna-kun!
Aldea...
I'll leave, for now.
Next time, you will be mine.
All Entrances on Okinawa have been sealed.
All enemy unit signals
have disappeared as well.
Amaterasu, and Scarlet of
the Masters, are all safe.
We win!
We did it, Kizuna!
You were so cool!
Hey!
Get away from him!
Yeah, it's thanks to all of you.
You actually did it with two girls at once...
How perverted!
N-No, it wasn't...
Oh, then what was it?
Just get away from him!
Next time, you will be mine.
Just who am I?
Illustration: Kenichiro Kasutani
An important mission is about to begin!
I wish I could be a little more useful, too.
What? You want me to go
in Aine-senpai's place?
That's your order as captain?
Next time: Academy Festa -First Live-
What do I do?
It's my first time, and I'm so excited!